let preguntas_facil = [
    {
      "categoria": "suma",
      "pregunta": "游꼝游꼝 + 游꼝",
      "respuesta": "游꼝游꼝游꼝",
      "incorrecta1": "游꼝游꼝",
      "incorrecta2": "游꼝游꼝游꼝游꼝",
      "incorrecta3": "游꼝游꼝游꼝游꼝游꼝",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    },
    {
      "categoria": "resta",
      "pregunta": "游꼛游꼛游꼛 - 游꼛",
      "respuesta": "游꼛游꼛",
      "incorrecta1": "游꼛游꼛游꼛",
      "incorrecta2": "游꼛",
      "incorrecta3": "游꼛游꼛游꼛游꼛",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    },
    {
      "categoria": "suma",
      "pregunta": "游꼙 + 游꼙游꼙",
      "respuesta": "游꼙游꼙游꼙",
      "incorrecta1": "游꼙游꼙",
      "incorrecta2": "游꼙游꼙游꼙游꼙",
      "incorrecta3": "游꼙游꼙游꼙游꼙游꼙",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    },
    {
      "categoria": "resta",
      "pregunta": "游꼖游꼖 - 游꼖",
      "respuesta": "游꼖",
      "incorrecta1": "游꼖游꼖",
      "incorrecta2": "游꼖游꼖游꼖",
      "incorrecta3": "游꼖游꼖游꼖游꼖",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    },
    {
      "categoria": "suma",
      "pregunta": "游꼟 + 游꼟",
      "respuesta": "游꼟游꼟",
      "incorrecta1": "游꼟游꼟游꼟游꼟",
      "incorrecta2": "游꼟游꼟游꼟",
      "incorrecta3": "游꼟游꼟游꼟游꼟游꼟",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    },
    {
      "categoria": "resta",
      "pregunta": "游꼡游꼡游꼡 - 游꼡",
      "respuesta": "游꼡游꼡",
      "incorrecta1": "游꼡游꼡游꼡",
      "incorrecta2": "游꼡",
      "incorrecta3": "游꼡游꼡游꼡",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    },
    {
      "categoria": "suma",
      "pregunta": "游꼘游꼘 + 游꼘游꼘",
      "respuesta": "游꼘游꼘游꼘游꼘",
      "incorrecta1": "游꼘游꼘游꼘游꼘游꼘游꼘",
      "incorrecta2": "游꼘游꼘游꼘游꼘游꼘",
      "incorrecta3": "游꼘游꼘游꼘游꼘游꼘游꼘游꼘",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    },
    {
      "categoria": "resta",
      "pregunta": "游꼚游꼚 - 游꼚",
      "respuesta": "游꼚",
      "incorrecta1": "游꼚游꼚",
      "incorrecta2": "游꼚游꼚游꼚",
      "incorrecta3": "游꼚游꼚游꼚游꼚",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    },
    {
      "categoria": "suma",
      "pregunta": "游볳 + 游볳",
      "respuesta": "游볳游볳",
      "incorrecta1": "游볳游볳游볳游볳",
      "incorrecta2": "游볳游볳游볳",
      "incorrecta3": "游볳游볳游볳游볳游볳",
      "objectFit": "cover",
      
    },
    {
      "categoria": "resta",
      "pregunta": "游본游본 - 游본",
      "respuesta": "游본",
      "incorrecta1": "游본游본",
      "incorrecta2": "游본游본游본",
      "incorrecta3": "游본游본游본游본游본游본",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    },
    {
      "categoria": "suma",
      "pregunta": "游꼛 + 游꼛游꼛游꼛",
      "respuesta": "游꼛游꼛游꼛游꼛",
      "incorrecta1": "游꼛游꼛游꼛游꼛游꼛",
      "incorrecta2": "游꼛游꼛游꼛游꼛游꼛游꼛游꼛",
      "incorrecta3": "游꼛游꼛游꼛游꼛游꼛游꼛",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    },
    {
      "categoria": "resta",
      "pregunta": "游꼠游꼠游꼠 - 游꼠游꼠",
      "respuesta": "游꼠",
      "incorrecta1": "游꼠游꼠",
      "incorrecta2": "游꼠游꼠游꼠",
      "incorrecta3": "游꼠游꼠游꼠游꼠",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    },
    {
      "categoria": "suma",
      "pregunta": "游봀 + 游봀游봀游봀",
      "respuesta": "游봀游봀游봀游봀",
      "incorrecta1": "游봀游봀游봀游봀游봀",
      "incorrecta2": "游봀游봀游봀游봀游봀游봀",
      "incorrecta3": "游봀游봀游봀游봀游봀游봀游봀游봀",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    },
    {
      "categoria": "suma",
      "pregunta": "游꼜 + 游꼜游꼜游꼜",
      "respuesta": "游꼜游꼜游꼜游꼜",
      "incorrecta1": "游꼜游꼜游꼜游꼜游꼜",
      "incorrecta2": "游꼜游꼜游꼜游꼜游꼜游꼜",
      "incorrecta3": "游꼜游꼜游꼜游꼜游꼜游꼜游꼜游꼜",
      "objectFit": "cover",
    }
  ];
  